RUDOLF IVANKOVIC

EXPERIENCED WEB & MOBILE DEVELOPER

AREAS OF EXPERTISE

Languages:

JavaScript, TypeScript, PHP, Python

Front-end Frameworks:

React, Vue, Electron, Flutter Web

Back-end Frameworks:

Node.js, Express, Nest.js, Net, Laravel, Django

Mobile App Frameworks:

React Native, Flutter

Cloud Services:

AWS Amplify, AWS Lambda, Amazon DynamoDB, S3, AWS Cognito, EC2, Cloud Firestore, Firebase Realtime database, Firebase gateway

DevOps:

Github, Gitlab, Bitbucket, Docker, CI/CD, Webpack, Jest, Mocha, Agile, Scrum, Kanban, Waterfall, TDD, SOLID, DRYy

Engineering & Technology:

Software Engineering, Reverse Engineering, Artificial Intelligence

CONTACT DETAILS

ADDRESS:

Karlovac, Karlovac, Croatia

LINKEDIN:

www.linkedin.com/in/rudolf-l-ivankovic-

EMAIL:

ivankovicrudolf12egmail.com

PERSONAL PROFILE

Experienced and detail-oriented Web & Mobile App Developer with a knack for conceptualizing and delivering elegant, user-friendly solutions effectively and efficiently.

Have 8 years of experience as a Full Stack Developer, specialized in Modern JS and PHP frameworks.

Love to collaborate with team actively, eager to take a challenge with new technologies and Having creative collaboration.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

WEB/MOBILE DEVELOPER

Self Employed | May 2021 - Present

REACT/NODE DEVELOPER

Code & Care | Feb 2019 - May 2021

- Improved a FinTech platform on the Frontend side and API implementation in React
- Developed mobile app from desktop web version with Firebase
- Added 30+ components to be used in the global app by using styled-components
- Redesigned global state management system with Redux thunk
- Simplified and improved UX from new design
- Improved performance by optimizing codes with modern JS and API handling
- Developed Admin panel with React and Node

FULL-STACK DEVELOPER

Code & Care | Sep 2017 - Feb 2019

- Developed headless CMS with React.js, Node.js, and Strapi
- Upgraded a powerful SaaS using Vue.js and Vuex, Vuetify framework
- Updated and added new RESTful APIs by using Apollo GraphQL + AWS Lambda function
- Improved search algorithm and architecture (+30% Big O)

- Implemented Aherf service for SEO and added JSON-LD for better search user experience.
- Increased CTR(Clickthrough rate) depends on A/B tests (+24% improved)
- Integrated payment gateway (stripe API) and localized by using i18n
- Transformed localStorage-based state management to Vue xbased system - Contributed to the in-browser slide generator and renderer using VueJS

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

PureNet | Aug 2015 - Sep 2017

- Acted as a Full Stack developer in a 30+ dev team for 2 years
- Improved UI/UX with React, Node, styled-components, d3.js,TradingView
- Developed and improved performance of +10 animation effects with custom styling
- Simplified global state management by using Mobx
- Suggested and Integrated real-time communication mechanism with Socket.IO and ws(npm package)

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

Endava| Feb 2014- Aug 2016

- Developed the front-end featuring rich web interface implemented using JavaScript libraries like jQuery & used Mustache Templating system.
- Developed a huge multi-advertisement layout engine that was cross-browser compatible.
- Used the Mozilla, Firefox extension, Firebug, to view and debug HTML, DOM, and JavaScript.
- Redesigned and implemented complete web applications to meet web and industry standards.
- Designed web pages using with HTML/HTML5, CSS/CSS3 and jQuery based on the W3C standard.
- Developed and improved applications using MVC Framework.
- Developed CSS page layouts, styles, and tableless coding for efficient design.

EDUCATION

COMPUTER SCIENCE | BACHELOR'S DEGREE RIT Croatia | 2011 - 2015